<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!-- Notes for localization -->
<!-- Please keep the overall structure and the tags like <note>, <item>,
     <module> unchanged, and basically translate the text.
     You could also add HTML tags with namespace specified, like <xhtml:a>
     instead of <a>. -->
<!-- For each note, keep the attribute "version" unchanged, and you could
     translate the "localized-version" attribute. -->

<notes xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<note version="nightly" localized-version="Development build">
<item>Please view <xhtml:a href="http://code.google.com/p/foxtrick/source/list">commit history</xhtml:a> at Google Code for details.</item>
</note>

<note version="0.8.2">
<item>Korean locale (SI-CH)</item>
<item>Lithuanian locale (LA-MJ)</item>
<item>General locale cleaning (CatzHoek)</item>
<item>Added links to <xhtml:a href="http://www.htev.org/">http://htev.org/</xhtml:a> statistics page.</item>
<item>Other trivial fixes. (convincedd, CatzHoek)</item>
</note>

<note version="0.8.1">
<item><module>ElectionTable</module>: adapted to new election page layout. (convincedd, ryanli)</item>
<item><module>HTThreadMarker</module>: new style. (convincedd, ryanli)</item>
<item><module>TableSort</module>: prevent conflicting with Hattrick's sorting. (convincedd)</item>
<item><module>HTMSPrediction</module>, <module>CopyRatings</module>: adapted to new match report layout. (convincedd)</item>
<item><module>LineupShortcut</module>: also show for non-supporters now. (ryanli)</item>
<item><module>TransferSearchResultFilters</module>: fix after latest changes. (convincedd)</item>
<item><module>SkillTable</module>: include loyalty and mother club bonus. (convincedd)</item>
</note>

<note version="0.8">
<item>Arabic locale. (GM-OmaniMilani)</item>
<item>New mechanism for viewing modules by page, old module OnPagePrefs thereby removed. (convincedd, ryanli)</item>
<item><xhtml:a href="#tab=main">Option</xhtml:a> not to load XML data from Hattrick. Also XMLs are now cached and an option to clear the cache has been added to the approriate pages (convincedd)</item>
<item>New module <module>LocalTime</module> for showing time in local timezone. (ryanli)</item>
<item>New module <module>LinksYouthLeague</module> for links at youth league page. (Parminu)</item>
<item>New module <module>CopyYouth</module> merges old youth copy modules, and provide link to destinations. New function for copying youth fixtures. (ryanli, Parminu)</item>
<item>New module <module>SupporterStatsEnhancements</module> which enhances display in supporter statistics. (convincedd)</item>
<item>Option to hide the invitation box visible on left sidebar in module <module>FixcssProblems</module>. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Option to reduce the height of my calendar in module <module>FixcssProblems</module>. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Link to CHPP management page in module <module>ExtraShortcuts</module>. (ljushaff)</item>
<item>Option to show colourised youth skills in module <module>SkillTable</module>. (foulpelz)</item>
<item>Option to play a sound in module <module>LiveAlert</module>. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Option to show team icons in module <module>MyMonitor</module>, and teams are now sortable. (convincedd)</item>
<item>Options to insert FoxTrick debug logs into postings in module <module>ForumYouthIcons</module>. (convincedd)</item>
<item>Option to load friendly book status on default in module <module>ShowFriendlyBooked</module>, enabled by default. (convincedd)</item>
<item>Link to load extra player information in module <module>SkillTable</module>. (convincedd)</item>
<item>In Firefox the FoxTrick icon was moved to the address bar and is draggable. (ryanli)</item>
<item>In Chrome the FoxTrick icon was moved inside the address bar. Also flickering has been removed and the speed improved. (convincedd)</item>
<item>FoxTrick enabled for Fennec/Firefox for mobile. (convincedd)</item>
<item>Beta versions of FoxTrick available now for Opera and Safari. (convincedd, ryanli)</item>
<item>Other trivial fixes and enhancements. (convincedd, ryanli)</item>
</note>

<note version="0.7.2">
<item>Links for comparing teams at Alltid in module <module>LinksTeam</module>. (convincedd)</item>
<item>Fixes for skill table at transfer search results. (convincedd, ryanli)</item>
</note>

<note version="0.7.1">
<item>Module <module>LeagueNewsFilter</module> split into <module>LeagueNewsFilter</module> and <module>ShowLineupSet</module>. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Modifications to adapt for new transfer search results page. (ryanli, taised)</item>
<item>Locale updates. (ryanli, CoRrRan, ljushaff, _KOHb_, slader, ElChiquitin)</item>
<item>Some other trivial fixes. (ryanli)</item>
</note>

<note version="0.7">
<item>Icelandic locale. (LA-LordBastard)</item>
<item>Vlaams locale copied from Dutch. (ryanli)</item>
<item>New module category, <xhtml:a href="#tab=information_aggregation">Information Aggregation</xhtml:a>. (ryanli)</item>
<item>New module <module>MyMonitor</module> for monitoring recent matches of selected teams at My Hattrirck. (ryanli)</item>
<item>New module <module>MarkAllAsRead</module>, a button to mark threads in all forums as read. (ryanli)</item>
<item>New module <module>ShowFriendlyBooked</module> for showing whether a team has booked a friendly on series page. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Rewrite of module <module>TickerAlert</module>, integrating former FoxtrickAlert, AlertCustomSound, AlertCustomOff modules. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Module <module>MatchPlayerColouring</module> loads match lineup from XML. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Module FoxtrickLineupShortcut renamed to <module>LineupShortcut</module>. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Module htmsStatistics renamed to <module>HTMSPrediction</module>. (ryanli)</item>
<item>New option in module <module>FriendlyInterface</module> to hide the secretary if he has nothing to report. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Module <module>StaffMarker</module> now uses <xhtml:a href="http://www.json.org/">JavaScript Object Notation</xhtml:a> for custom markers. (ryanli)</item>
<item>New radios in module <module>ExtraShortcuts</module>, Balkaradio and Downtime Radio. (ljushaff, ryanli)</item>
<item>Option of <module>LeagueAndMatchChat</module> to open Yaplet chat in a frame removed. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Various trivial fixes. (ryanli, Mod-spambot)</item>
</note>

<note version="0.6.2">
<item>Module <module>SeriesFlags</module> now fetches team data directly from Hattrick. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Locale updates. (ljushaff, csajszi, Mod-spambot)</item>
<item>Some other trivial fixes. (ryanli)</item>
</note>

<note version="0.6.1">
<item>Module <module>HTMSPoints</module> now calculates points locally without connecting to HTMS website. (taised)</item>
<item>Module <module>htmsStatistics</module> now loads prediction correctly. (taised)</item>
<item>Locale updates. (Mod-spambot, Mod-OmaniMilani, Baler0, ljushaff, _KOHb_, Slash-ss, MEO_Comandante)</item>
<item>Compatible with Firefox 4.2 branch. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Some other trivial fixes. (ryanli)</item>
</note>

<note version="0.6">
<item>New preferences interface. (ryanli)</item>
<item>OAuth interface implemented for the new Hattrick CHPP API. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Module <module>LiveAlert</module> for alerting at HT Live goals. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Module <module>OldStyleFace</module> for showing faces in old Hattrick style. (Aimo_Kanuuna)</item>
<item>Module <module>NtPeek</module> for peeking NT/U20 matches at My Hattrick. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Module <module>SeriesFlags</module> for showing user country and series beside manager and team links. Images provided by <xhtml:a href="http://www.fantamondi.it/HTMS/">HTMS</xhtml:a>. (taised, ryanli)</item>
<item>Module <module>HTMSPoints</module> for showing player's <xhtml:a href="http://www.fantamondi.it/HTMS/index.php?page=nt&amp;lang=en">HTMS Points</xhtml:a>, i.e. numeralized ability and potential. (taised)</item>
<item>Module <module>FriendlyInterface</module> with options for showing player's full name in match line up page and showing national teams in links for NT players. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Module HighlightBotTeams renamed to <module>HighlightOwnerless</module>. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Module YouthSkillNotes and ShortPA removed. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Option to hide forum sneak-peek in <module>FixcssProblems</module>. (ljushaff)</item>
<item>Option to copy advertisement in non-table style in <module>CopyPlayerAd</module>. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Option to show HatStats per rating in <module>Ratings</module>. (taised)</item>
<item>Belarusian locale. (LA-Stolik)</item>
<item>Add some frequently asked questions at <xhtml:a href="#tab=help">Help tab</xhtml:a>. (ryanli)</item>
<item>New grey icon for report links. (ljushaff)</item>
<item><module>YouthPromotes</module> also shows the earliest date to promote a player. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Most features working under Google Chrome. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Some trivial fixes for latest Hattrick changes. (ryanli, taised, ljushaff)</item>
<item>Module <module>TeamSelectBox</module> disabled by default. (ryanli)</item>
<item>Module <module>SmallerPages</module> disabled by default. (ljushaff)</item>
<item>Radio options in <module>ExtraShortcuts</module> are disabled by default. (ryanli)</item>
</note>
</notes>
